Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
Love's Chocolate Cosmos
'Sup, Natsume! Morning.
M-Morning.
Nice, is this new?
I borrowed it from my sister.
That's cool.
One minor new development...
Figures why it's girly.
Is it weird?
I made a friend besides Himari.
Nah, you pull it off.
By the way, where's Himari-chan?
I haven't seen her yet—
Ha! Gotcha!
H-Himari?
Hey, Himari-chan. Morning!
Morning!
You two besties seem to be getting along.
"Look at you, getting friendly
with the side bestie."
"I thought I was number one,
but I see how it is."
Is that it?
Hey, nice coat.
Where'd you get it?
It's his sister's.
Oh, no wonder it's so cute.
Before I knew it, we were a group of three.
Yu!
It's almost time for the Christmas exhibit!
Have you decided on the flowers?
F-For the most part.
My life's been fun
ever since meeting Himari.
As long as she likes my work, it's worth it.
Hey, about Christmas...
Himari-chan mentioned
having plans that day, right?
What? Really?
She said she was coming to the exhibit.
Natsume, I've got a huge favor to ask.
Could I have some time alone
with Himari-chan on Christmas?
It's not like she needs
to be at the exhibit.
Besides, I don't want Himari
hating romance forever.
So I lied and said that the
exhibit was canceled.
I hope it works out between them.
Natsume-kun, let's grab some lunch.
Ramen
Kadoya
Sensei.
Say you had a friend that
was better off with someone else.
I think true friendship
is about letting them
spend time with that
other person over yourself.
What do you think?
Hmm...
It's like with flowers.
Sometimes, flowers grow better
when you plant two or three seeds together.
Instead of just one by itself.
Wait, is that even true?
Hey, you!
No slacking at the reception desk.
Wh-What are you doing here?
I visited your place
and they said you were here.
Yeah... well...
Why didn't you hang out with him?
I did. Not for long, though.
I only went because he said you'd be there.
By the way, what was that all about?
He was all serious
and confessed his love to me.
So gross. That kind of tactic is the worst.
B-But he's a good guy.
I was just hoping you two
would be happy together.
Yu, are you serious?
That guy used you to get closer to me.
He's been trying to get with me
before you and I started hanging out.
I kept quiet hoping he genuinely
wanted to be friends with you.
So no more cheating on me, okay?
Who's cheating?
Is this one yours?
How did you know?
Don't tell me, was I your main inspo?
Wh-Why do you ask?
The meaning of my name.
"Himari" means "sunflower."
Th-That's just a coincidence.
I lied.
I made that piece for Himari.
The sunflowers mean...
"I only see you."
Like Himari's friendship.
Straight as an arrow.
Hey, Yu.
If you care about me,
don't go trying to set me up.
Huh?
If I end up with someone else,
that would leave you all alone.
That's not good.
You and I are best friends.
But there's no way we'd each
find someone at the same time.
Probably!
But we should fix
that bad habit of yours first.
I guess I'll do my best.
Promise you'll only see me forever?
I'm your only best friend after all.
Bwa-ha!
So?
What do you think about this wreath?
Hmm... Five out of ten!
It's good, but it feels incomplete.
I wish you'd get to know me better first.
One day, when you feel complete...
Promise to show me first!
Ever since I was little,
I was always bad at making stuff.
Hey, look at that cutie.
Whatever. The world's full of
good-looking people.
Even a pretty girl like me
has worries on her mind.
This one needs water, too.
Chocolate cosmos.
Obviously, they smell like chocolate.
They bloom in the fall.
Yu!
Good morning!
Morning!
He's texting Enocchi.
Hey, Yu?
'S-Sup, Himari. Morning.
Hey, it's dangerous to text while you walk.
R-Right...
Look up already!
It's like he's glued to the screen.
I'm not giving up, though!
Have any plans for summer break?
Oh yeah, it starts soon.
Accessories are great and all,
but next year will be all
about entrance exams.
This may be our last summer to have fun!
Wanna spend the night, just the two of us?
A-A-Are you stupid?
We can't do that!
Why not? We're best friends!
Nothing can come between us!
S-Sure, but still...
Or let me guess.
Are you actually into me like that?
O-Of course not.
Stop, Yu!
I'm just jokin—
Morning, Hii-chan.
Oh hey, Enocchi.
Let's go, Yu-kun!
Y-Yeah.
Hii-chan, I can't wait for our sleepover!
What's on my mind, you ask?
Yu's been too busy paying attention
to Enocchi recently.
Yu-kun! Open wide!
Ahh...
I-I think that's enough.
I found somewhere away from others
so you wouldn't get embarrassed.
Yeah, but still...
It's embarrassing enough
without anyone watching.
I wouldn't complain too much, if I were you.
Enomoto-san, help!
Enomoto-san, HELP
Himari was waiting for me!
Himari was waiting for me.
Please! Please text back.
Himari's talking about a sleepover.
I can't do this anymore, she's too cute.
I'm gonna lose my best friend.
Don't leave me on read
I'll do anything!
Please help
I feel violated.
That drink isn't allowed when it's just us.
It's rude to bring
in reminders of another girl.
Here.
Don't say it like that.
She's my rival at this point!
If you find her too cute to be her friend,
just tell her how you feel.
Yu-kun, do you even want to date Hii-chan?
I dunno.
I like Himari, but opening
my store comes before love.
Yup, you tend to make
things difficult like that.
But I admire that.
It means you want both love and your dream.
You're so honest with yourself,
and I love that about you.
Take your sweet time with Hii-chan.
That way, I still have a chance to catch up!
I wish I had that mental fortitude.
Everyone's busy practicing
for the tournament.
Yu!
Let's go shopping when
you're done watering flowers!
Himari's soft, supple skin!
Calm down, this is nothing new!
Shopping? What for?
Yup! I want a swimsuit for summer break!
S-Swimsuit? Are you crazy?!
Asking a guy you're not even dating
to help you pick out a swim—
Hang on.
I did that last year.
What was I even thinking back then?
Then let's invite Enomoto-san.
Why Enocchi?
Never mind, that's fine.
You'd probably invite her anyways.
Th-Then I'll go find her!
Hey, Enomoto-san.
Himari's arch nemesis, Iron Claw!
Ouch...
"Himari wants to shop for swimsuits.
Help, Enomoto-san!"
You're not inviting me to see
me in a swimsuit, are you?
I-I'm sorry!
This seemed like a "Bwa-ha!" situation,
so I recruited your support.
Don't go then.
B-But she's my best friend.
"All that genuine talk for what?"
"You're like any other guy."
I wanna see Himari in a swimsuit. Sue me.
I have band practice today,
so you'll have to survive on your own.
O-Okay.
That's cute!
You're way too close!
Yu, what do you think?
I-I should go hom—
Come on!
You're choking me!
Pick something out yourself!
You're not one to care what others think.
Yeah, but...
I'm getting this to show you.
I wanna get something you'll like.
O-Oh.
What's this, Yu-kun?
Are you blushing, by chance?
Sh-Shut up.
Stop teasing me like that.
Bwa-ha!
I swear, you'll fall for that forever.
Let's go inside!
Y-Yeah, let's start over there.
The innocent dress type?
Or the vibrant two-piece?
Look at all these florals!
Which one do you like?
Touché, Himari!
She knows I like cute designs
more than raunchy ones!
Th-They all look fine.
Then lemme try them on!
I feel so uncomfortable...
Yu!
Y-You done?
Guess what?
I actually have a super
raunchy piece on right now.
You weren't looking at anything like that!
Oh, but I was!
With tiny straps.
Y-You liar!
They don't even sell those designs out here!
You sure about that?
Th-This is where she usually goes, "Bwa-ha!"
But what if she's telling
the truth? I'd die!
S-Sorry, gotta go!
I chickened out.
How can she pull that shit in public?
Hey, idiot.
You have a guest.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kureha Enomoto.
Shinji-kun's told me all about you, Yu-chan.
I've heard you're good friends with Rion.
Kureha-san, you know Makishima?
Yup, we're old neighbors.
Oh...
So, Kureha.
What's your visit about?
Right, I totally forgot.
Can I have your Himari-chan? Pretty please?
Scumbag womanizer. Come here.
Hey. Yu's been acting weird lately.
You got in his head again, didn't you?
Natsu? Acting weird?
He's been avoiding me like the plague.
And he always makes sure Enocchi tags along.
Well isn't it obvious?
Natsu's finally fed up with you.
He's switched over to Rin-chan.
Would you bet your racket on that?
Wait.
No roughhousing with the racket.
Ugh, that's totally unfair.
Give me my racket.
To tell you the truth,
I haven't done anything.
Or rather, I have no reason to do anything.
Luckily, Kureha-san took care of that.
The chocolate cosmos represents...
"The end of love."
I'm sure you've heard about this,
but Himari-chan was
supposed to join our agency.
She made it sound like she was coming,
then suddenly quit out of nowhere.
I-I'm sorry to cause you trouble.
It's okay. I'm not mad.
I only came up with the idea
and convinced the CEO.
And funded all expenses out of pocket.
All to get kicked
to the curb by Himari-chan.
Why would I be mad?
I came to talk business with you, Yu-chan.
Business?
Can you talk to Himari-chan
so she joins our agency?
But Himari and I have—
I've heard.
You have a dream to open your own store.
But this is the middle of nowhere.
Don't you think that's a bit unrealistic?
I'm not asking you to give that up for free.
What's that for?
Duh, silly!
It's in exchange for Himari-chan.
I'll pay you cash in advance
for her future earnings.
Oh right! And models, too.
You'll need a girl to take her place.
Feel free to pick anyone
you like from our agency.
I've heard enough!
Himari isn't a thing you can buy!
No money or model will change my mind!
It's my dream to open
a store together with Himari.
If I can't do it with her,
none of it matters!
Oh, I get it.
She's super important to you.
I totally get why. She's so cute!
Honestly, it's pure talent.
But isn't it a shame?
She's basically squashing
that for someone else's mediocre talent.
Are you saying
I'm squashing Himari's talent?
Yup!
Honestly, even in middle school,
your pieces were pretty amateur.
And your work now
is hardly more than ordinary.
You're crushing your best friend's
talent for selfish reasons.
Would you call that true friendship?
Oh, wait!
You're not business partners.
You just can't let Himari-chan go
because you like her.
Th-That's not true.
So what's your choice?
If you can devote your life to loving her,
I'll let you come to Tokyo with us.
But you'll have to give up your dream.
I don't think she's right.
But... could this be Himari's big break?
See, you can't commit either way.
You two just wanna have fun.
Neither of you are serious
about your dreams.
Stop right there!
I won't let you lay a finger on Yu-kun!
Hibari-kun.
Oops, I forgot to lock the door.
Hibari-san, how did you know?
Himari called, so I rushed over.
Kureha-kun, I see you've been toying
with my dear Yu-kun.
I would never! I was just talking business.
Business would involve merit
for both parties.
I see you haven't changed one bit.
Saku-nee-san, are those two...
True business is about
achieving mutual benefits.
Can't you tell? They're exes.
I won't allow Himari and Yu-kun's
friendship to suffer a single blow.
There's that tough guy front again.
Here.
Hibari-san?!
Stay out of it unless you want this
video plastered all over the internet.
Please, don't! Kureha-kun!
That has nothing to do with this!
You have nothing to do with this.
Remember how you swore off real women?
You can't touch my phone
as long as it's tucked in here.
Why you—!
Then... take this!
So scary!
Sakura-chan, here!
Don't drag me into this.
You can't blackmail me anymo—
I have twenty backups
for work, just in case!
You tricked me!
I've never seen this side of Hibari-san...
He's always been like this.
Why don't you two get back together already?
No way!
We're getting nowhere
with you two doing the talking.
Kureha, you may think
you're doing the right thing,
but you can't push your ideals onto others.
I get why you see yourself in Himari-chan.
But you hated being told what
to do more than anyone.
I knew I shouldn't have
asked Sakura-chan for help.
You're always the voice of reason.
I've changed my mind!
Yu-chan, let's go head to head.
Head to head?
Take the summer to make
your best masterpiece.
Prove me wrong with
the quality of your work.
You should be thanking me
for even considering this option.
What do you mean?
Like I said, I've been paying
for Himari-chan out of pocket.
I don't know any high schooler
who'd be able to pay this off.
Kureha, you mean
if my idiot brother said no,
you were planning to blackmail
Himari-chan with debt?
You're so smart, Sakura-chan! Yup!
The only person who can help Himari-chan
is her best friend Yu-chan.
Are you in?
If I win, will you wipe her slate clean?
Sure!
If I lose, I'll give up
Himari-chan and the money.
But if I win, hand her over to me.
Alright.
The theme is "memories of summer."
You have until the Obon festival in August.
I'll be back then!
Are my accessories really
worth Himari's devotion?
It was time to put that to the test.
The Meaning Behind Sunflowers